<root>
   <name>Grafana</name>
   <key>grafana</key>
   <state>stable</state>
   <logo>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/opensa-sa/grafana/master/log.png</logo>
   <description>
      <short>
         <en>This plugin is a modified version of the GLPI metabase plugin that allows you to embed Grafana dashboards directly into GLPI.</en>
         <es>Este plugin es una versi칩n modificada del plugin de Metabase para GLPI que permite incrustar paneles de Grafana directamente en GLPI.</es>
      </short>
      <long>
         <en>
This plugin lets you embed Grafana dashboards directly into your GLPI environment.
Inspired by the Metabase plugin for GLPI, it leverages the Grafana API to import and display your visualizations within the GLPI interface.
With this add-on, you can get a unified view of your monitoring and inventory data without having to switch between different applications.
It simplifies data management and analysis, making it a valuable tool for any IT administrator.
         </en>
         <es>
Este plugin te permite incrustar tableros de Grafana directamente en tu entorno GLPI.
Est치 inspirado en el plugin de Metabase para GLPI y aprovecha la API de Grafana para importar y mostrar tus visualizaciones dentro de la interfaz de GLPI.
Con este complemento, puedes tener una vista unificada de tus datos de monitoreo e inventario sin necesidad de alternar entre diferentes aplicaciones.
Simplifica la gesti칩n y el an치lisis de datos, lo que lo convierte en una herramienta valiosa para cualquier administrador de TI.
         </es>
      </long>
   </description>
   <homepage>https://github.com/Open-SA/grafana/</homepage>
   <download>https://github.com/Open-SA/grafana/releases</download>
   <issues>https://github.com/Open-SA/grafana/issues</issues>
   <readme>https://git.opensa.com.ar/opensa/glpi-plugins/grafana/-/blob/main/README.md</readme>
   <authors>
      <author>Open SA</author>
   </authors>
   <versions>
      <version>
         <num>1.0.0</num>
         <compatibility>~10.0.18</compatibility>
         <download_url>https://github.com/Open-SA/grafana/releases/download/1.0.0/glpi-grafana-1.0.0.tar.bz2</download_url>
      </version>
   </versions>
   <langs>
      <lang>en_US</lang>
      <lang>es_AR</lang>
  </langs>
   <license>GPLv2</license>
   <tags>
      <en>
         <tag>Reporting</tag>
         <tag>Data-vizualisation</tag>
         <tag>Business-intelligence</tag>
         <tag>Dashboard</tag>
         <tag>Statistics</tag>
         <tag>Central</tag>
      </en>
      <es>
         <tag>Reportes</tag>
         <tag>Visualidacion-de-Datos</tag>
         <tag>Inteligencia-de-Negocios</tag>
         <tag>Tableros</tag>
         <tag>Estadisticas</tag>
         <tag>Central</tag>
      </es>
   </tags>
   <screenshots>
      <screenshot>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Open-SA/grafana/master/screenshot.png</screenshot>
   </screenshots>
</root>